{
  "preserveQuestionOrder": false,
  "preserveRoundOrder": true,
  "author": "royal_flush",
  "questions": [
    {
      "category": "Space",
      "question": "'I'm unhappy about the space between Smith and and and and and Jones' is an example of what literary trope?",
      "correct": "Antanaclasis",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Epizeuxis",
        "Conduplicatio",
        "Mesodiplosis"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Space",
      "question": "'A Spaceman Came Travelling' is (apparently) a Christmas song by which artist?",
      "correct": "Chris de Burgh",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Lionel Richie",
        "Phil Collins",
        "Eric Clapton"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Space",
      "question": "'Space, is big. Really big.' is a line from a novel by which author?",
      "correct": "Douglas Adams",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Terry Pratchett",
        "Arthur C. Clarke",
        "Frank Herbert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Space",
      "question": "At the end of Portal 2 [spoiler alert], the Space Core gets stranded in space with Wheatley, a character voiced by which comedian?",
      "correct": "Stephen Merchant",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Robert Webb",
        "David Walliams",
        "Ed Byrne"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Space",
      "question": "Which of these is a TV sitcom created, written by and starring Simon Pegg and Jessica Stevenson?",
      "correct": "Spaced",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Space Jam",
        "Space Hopper",
        "Spaceman"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Time",
      "question": "The episode 'Once, Upon Time' featured in which 2021 Doctor Who serial?",
      "correct": "Flux",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Hydrax",
        "ATMOS",
        "Collision"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Time",
      "question": "'Exact time for life' is the slogan for which high-end watch brand?",
      "correct": "Omega",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Rolex",
        "TAG Heuer",
        "Patek Philippe"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Time",
      "question": "Which of these commercial flights would see you arrive before you leave?",
      "correct": "Hong Kong to San Francisco",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Canberra to Wellington",
        "Tokyo to Beijing",
        "Changi to Istanbul"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Time",
      "question": "'It was the best of times, it was the worst of times' is the opening line of which novel?",
      "correct": "A Tale of Two Cities",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Great Expectations",
        "Martin Chuzzlewit",
        "Bleak House"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Time",
      "question": "Who released the 1983 song 'Time After Time'?",
      "correct": "Cyndi Lauper",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cher",
        "Bonnie Tyler",
        "The Bangles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Power",
      "question": "Which party is currently in power in Australia?",
      "correct": "Labour",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Liberal",
        "Green",
        "Nationals"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Power",
      "question": "Who starred as Oz in the 2013 Sam Raimi film 'Oz the Great and Powerful'?",
      "correct": "James Franco",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Zach Braff",
        "Tobey Maguire",
        "Johnny Depp"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Power",
      "question": "In the late 1980s, Joseph Nye became the first person to make reference to what?",
      "correct": "Soft power",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Power vacuum",
        "Knowledge is power",
        "Power dressing"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Power",
      "question": "What is five raised to the fifth power?",
      "correct": "3,125",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "25",
        "120",
        "15,625"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Power",
      "question": "'With great power comes great responsibility' is an expression associated with which superhero?",
      "correct": "Spider-Man",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Superman",
        "Batman",
        "Iron Man"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Energy",
      "question": "In Einstein's famous formula E = mc^2, what does the 'c' represent?",
      "correct": "The speed of light",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Energy",
        "Mass",
        "Power"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Energy",
      "question": "Which of these is an energy drink?",
      "correct": "Monster Energy",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Vampire Energy",
        "Werewolf Energy",
        "Ghost Energy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Energy",
      "question": "Which electronic duo released the 2020 hit single 'Energy'?",
      "correct": "Disclosure",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Chemical Brothers",
        "Basement Jaxx",
        "Daft Punk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Energy",
      "question": "Though the term 'energise' is formally used for transporter commands, which of these lines has NEVER been said in Star Trek?",
      "correct": "Beam me up, Scotty",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Scotty, beam us up, fast",
        "Prepare to beam us up, Mr Scott",
        "Have Scotty beam us up"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Energy",
      "question": "How much energy would it take to raise the temperature of one kilogram of water by one degree celsius?",
      "correct": "42 Joules",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "420 Joules",
        "4,200 Joules",
        "42,000 Joules"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of these is NOT the name of one of Marvel's six Infinity Stones?",
      "correct": "Energy",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Power",
        "Time",
        "Space"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of these would score nine points when played without bonus tiles in a standard game of UK Scrabble?",
      "correct": "Space",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Energy",
        "Power",
        "Time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "In 1973, Jim Croce sang about what '...in a Bottle'?",
      "correct": "Time",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Energy",
        "Power",
        "Space"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which word features in a Fox Kids TV show that debuted on August 28th 1993?",
      "correct": "Power",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Energy",
        "Time",
        "Space"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What was the category of round two of DangerZone today?",
      "correct": "Time",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Energy",
        "Power",
        "Space"
      ]
    }
  ]
}